challenges = [
    {
        question: "What HTML element do we use to import JavaScript?",
        answers: [
            "<script>",
            "<javascript>",
            "<scripting>",
            "<js>"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "Where is the correct place to insert JavaScript?",
        answers: [
            "The <head> section",
            "The <body> section",
            "Both the <head> section and <body> section are correct"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How can you detect the application name of the clientâ€™s browser?",
        answers: [
            "navigator.appName",
            "navigator.browserName",
            "browser.appName",
            "browser.name"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following is correct?",
        answers: [
            "i =+ 1",
            "i = i++1;",
            "+i+;",
            "i += 1;"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which array method sorts the elements of an array?",
        answers: [
            "sort()",
            "changeOrder(order)",
            "order()",
            "None of the others"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "How do you open a new window with JavaScript?",
        answers: [
            "window.new(...);",
            "open(new window());",
            "window.open(...);",
            "window.open_new(...);"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following event occurs when the user clicks on an HTML element?",
        answers: [
            "onchange",
            "onclick",
            "onmouseover",
            "onmouseclick"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How do you get a DOM element by id in JavaScript?",
        answers: [
            "window.getElementById(...)",
            "document.getElementById(...)",
            "page.getElementById(...)",
            "document.innerHTML.getElementById(...)"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How do you create a new function in JavaScript?",
        answers: [
            "myFunction() {}",
            "function:myFunction() {}",
            "new.function() {}",
            "function myFunction() {}"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Can you set the style of an HTML tag by using JavaScript?",
        answers: [
            "yes",
            "no"
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
];
